Yay!
Hey!
Where are you?
Ready, old man?
Hey, nice.
Nice win.
Ha-ha-ha!
Oh, no!
What should I do?
Yay!
Yoo-hoo! Where'd it go?
Grandpa, behind you...
Kanamin's behind you.
Let's go!
Hitaka's driving!
Where's the hallway?
Here, here...
This is it.
I don't think you saw it.
You can't see the view yet.
Oh?
That's it.
You didn't see it.
But I think you will.
That man, Mr. 00.
Mr. 00?
Yes, that's Mr. 00.
No, no, no. How long has it been?
About an hour and a half.
He's celebrating his birthday.
Are you gonna be okay?
Are you okay?
I'm fine.
Are you sure everyone's okay?
Super comfortable.
Super secure.
I'm comfortable.
To all of you.
I'm not drunk about once every 30 minutes.
I'm not drunk.
I'm just checking all the time.
You know what I'm saying?
I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
I can't even see the screen.
I can't see it.
I press this button, and the light comes on again.
If you push it...
Oh, oh, oh, oh.
So I can see the outside screen here like this?
Yeah, you can see both.
It's the newest one.
You can see it.
Okay, so you do it like this.
Like this.
Do it like this.
Driving in Hokkaido Originally, on the contrary, that's all there really was, wasn't it?
It wasn't on the front page.
Yoo-hoo!
That's a lot.
Karami's getting so tiny.
We've already done the shopping.
I know what I'm going to make.
I'm looking forward to it.
I wonder if there's a campsite open.
I hope so.
Okay, I'm off.
Yes, sir! We're here!
Kanami's getting ready!
Do you want to leave your phone?
Sure, put it down.
You're in Yamanashi, right?
That's right.
I'm getting the rabbit ready.
Getting ready.
I realized I didn't turn the camera on halfway through.
That's right.
Well, if that's the way it's gonna be.
Looking good, looking good, looking good.
I think I need a flat surface.
Can I leave it here?
Yeah, sure.
This is it.
Bamboo branches.
Oh, my God.
Careful.
It's done.
And...
Children in need.
This is
I'm going to use it.
Let's see if we're still going.
Here we go.
Hitoko, what's this?
That.
I thought there was some kind of dog in it.I thought there was some kind of dog in there.
First...
There's a dog in here.
A chair.
Oh, you're going to put it on?
A fancy one.
I see what you mean.
Here.
It's very special.
Isn't it pretty?
It's adorable.
Oh, I see. My jacket.
Can I take this out?
Jacket?
This one?
Yeah! That's the pot.
Oh, it smells so good.
I can see it. I can see it.
Oh, what's this?
Looks like it could be a book!
Long Phong
Oh, Night Mall
Okay, it's gonna look great.
It's gonna look good?
It's gonna look great.
Here we go.
I'm gonna batten down the hatches.
Sometimes there are bugs on it.
Oh, yeah.
I think I'll use this.
Split the wood into little pieces.
Split the wood?
Yes, yes, yes.
Split the tree.
Okay.
Thank you for watching.
Oh!
Oh, wow, wow, wow.
Like this.
Make the tree smaller.
Oh, wow.
Do it.
You want to do it?
I want to do it.
You want to? I want to do it.
Oh!
My heart is in the right place.
Like this, maybe I can do it.
Here.
Hand, for not cutting it by mistake.
Yeah.
A little bit.
I think it's around here.
And this big piece of wood.
The one that splits this?
Yeah, I'm gonna split this one.
A little more like this.
Like this... at the back.
And here, in the front.
Yeah, hit it with the tripod.
Yeah.
Oh!
Go, go, go, go, go.
Go, go, go, go, go, go.
It takes a lot of strength.
You can do it.
All right. All right.
It's okay, it's okay, it's okay. Here it comes. Here it comes.
Come on. Come on.
Okay.
Nice.
You win.
It's stuck.
Yay!
Batoning.
I got the batoning!
We did it!
What fun!
See you later.
Because there's only one of each.
And since there's only two
Then there's one of you
While you're batoning me.
Me and Peyo.
I'm going to make dinner.
I'll cook.
Let's cook.
Ta-da!
Tomato casserole
Now, put the ingredients here.
Vegetables you can buy at the store
Good for times like this.
Can I just put them in there now?
It's good, isn't it?
And chicken.
Chicken with vegetables and raw chicken.
Okay, chicken first.Okay, so chicken first.
I think it's okay to put the chicken in first.
Just put the chicken in.
I'm going to do this right now.
Put the chicken on the bottom and the chicken on top.
How much? Just by eye.
I'm sure.
By eye.
measuring by eye
Recommendation
This way
This way.
How many to put in?
Amount by eye
by eye
Producing Pole
3.2.1
1 piece
2 pieces?
yes.
And if it's not enough...
I'll tell you.
I'll talk.
Is it cold?
Yeah, it's cold.
Can I, can I go?
Yeah, you can go.
But when the fire comes up...
Hey, yeah.
But there's a little bit of wind.
Yeah, I guess so.
How much? Tomato juice.
Can I put a couple of consommé in it?
Yeah, two consommé.
But, you know, if it's too thin.
But, you know, more tomato juice is better than more water.
It's good. You want to put it all in?
Yes, you can put it in.
We're gonna eat it anyway.
Wow.
Topping.
No, it's not.
You scared the shit out of me.
I thought it was a cat.
Which one?
Doesn't the soda on this chair make it look like a cat?
I don't know. I think I've got an avatar.
That's what I'm struggling with.
I'm supposed to just mash the end of my hand like this and light it on fire.
I can't do this right now.
I've never been able to do it right.
It's hard.
And?
I'm gonna light it.
I'm going to light this one.
Three days.
It shakes.
The fire fell.
The fire's out.
I'll get him up.
Please wake me up.
I'll wake him up. I'll wake him up. I'll wake him up.
Let's see if I can wake him up.
Oh, it's okay. It's okay. It's okay.
It's okay. It's okay. It's okay.
Oh, it's good, it's good, it's good.
Good, good, good. No, no, no.
How's it going? What do you think, Kange's friend?
Are you looking at me right now?
Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah.
So I'm going to start a fire now.
Cheer for me.
I'm rooting for you.
You okay? - I'm fine.
Yeah, I'm fine. I'm fine.
Hang in there.
Come on, come on, come on.
Wow, wow, wow, wow.
You're gonna get some awesome flowers.
What?
What? Oh, my God.
What? I wanted to take a video of that.
Ha-ha-ha-ha.
Shutter chance.
What? Oh, no.
What? Cool.
Good night.
We're here, we're here, we're here!
We're here!
Maybe, maybe, maybe.
I mean, it's burning.
It's getting warmer.
No, it's not.
Big spunk.
What's that?what's that?
Whoo.
Hoo.
Ha-ha-ha-ha-ha.
I'm scared.
You're gonna watch it later? Maybe from cheering.
It feels so good to give birth.
I'll feel the same way in an instant.
It'd be awful if the wind blew it away.
It's coming from this way.
I think it's on.
Yeah, I think I'm on it.
It looks really good right in the middle.
I think it's on.
Oh, my God! It's coming, it's coming, it's coming.
Oh, my God!
I'm really excited.
Here it comes, here it comes! We're here!
We're here!
It's gonna get warm in here.
You're welcome.
Here we are.
It really is a little warm.
Maybe my seat is the warmest.
Oh, yeah.
I'll sit here. It's warmer.
We're here!
Yay.
Okay, okay, here we are.
Is it warm? Nice and warm.
Nice? Yeah, it's good.
My nose is red.
I'm so cold.
You want to do it?
Spread the fire?
I'm spreading the fire.
But we're not there yet. We're not there yet.
I see what you mean.
Oh!
That's funny.
Kanamin, are you okay not being a voice actor?
This is so funny.
Thanks. I'll keep it on and off.
Let's eat marshmallows.
I'll have some.
Calitro is good.
Caritas. - Caritas.
High heat.
Do it this way?
It's more elastic than I thought.
What's that? What?
It shakes so much.
It swings.
Oh, my God.
It's got a lot of firepower.
It'll get stronger.
It's not strong enough.
It'll warm up.
Cheers!
Yeah!
Whoo!
Oh, it's gonna burn!
Oh, yeah? Seriously!
There you go! Wow!
That's real!
I totally see where the fire hit.
Wow!
Wow! That's amazing! Oh, my God! It's gonna burn! It's gonna burn!
Laughter.
You're good.
Oh, I'm burnt.
I'm burnt out.
Do you want another one?
Yeah, I'll eat it.
I don't know what to do.
Hey, I'm sorry.
I'm so sad.
Who's this?
You're high!
I don't know...
It's so hard!
That's a marshmallow with a memory.
Do it again?
Oh, no.
Let's just try this one.
It's so hot. It's so hot.
Delicious. Let's try it again.
This one's good. Delicious.
Shall we go somewhere else?
I don't think I'm cut out for this. Oh, there's Mom.
Hello?
I put it on.
Boom.although
but
I'm eating marshmallows.
I'm eating a marshmallow.
Now?
Not at all.
How's it going?
On speaker.
Laughing.
It's so much fun.
I could drive safely.
Not at all.
I like this one.
Yes, thank you!
It's good, but you have to make it.
Amazing!
Oh, no, no, no!
It's burnt.
That's not so bad.
Oh, burnt.
Are you okay with the cold?
Yeah, I'm fine.
Oh, it's totally warm now.
Is it getting warmer?
Hey, hey, hey.
Try one and see what happens.
It's black.
I'm sorry it burned a little bit.
Bon appétit!
Delicious.
Delicious!
Slowly, slowly, slowly...
Mmm...
Burn. It's on fire.
Are you okay?
It's good.
So slow and steady.
It's good. - It's good.
Yummy?
Soft.
Hard? Still hard?
Yeah, it's fine.
Are you okay?
It's so good.
You two are so cute.
I could eat marshmallows with this.
Oh, really?
Oh, right, the regular marshmallows.
Crunchy?
Yeah, they're good.
It's good.
Even the burnt bits.
Oh, was it good? Was it okay?
It smells good.
Did I look like this before?
I guess I'm okay.
Do you want to wear a hat, Calamin?
Do you have a hat? I have this one.
Do you have another one? I have another one.
You want one? You want to wear it?
Can I? I want to wear it.
You want to put it on?
Mmm-hmm.
Mmm?
me
me me me me